{"data":{"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"5414","name":"Eatori Market","address":"1215 Griswold St","zipcode":"48226","owner":"Zak Yatim","licenseNumber":"221004","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","mostRecentLicenseDate":"4/27/2018","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"High","reviewFrequencyDays":"180.0","geom":"0101000020E6100000E8F3040133C354C0080982AE9A2A4540","inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"45010","establishmentid":"5414","name":"Eatori Market","inspectionDate":"2019-01-25T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"124","pcount":"0","pfcount":"1","ccount":"1","criticalcount":"1","noncritical":"1","correctedcritical":"1","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"45010","inspectionDate":"1/25/2019","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"5414","name":"Eatori Market","violationCode":"3-501.15","violationDescription":"(A) Cooling shall be accomplished in accordance with the time and temperature criteria specified under § 3-501.14 by using one or more of the following methods based on the type of FOOD being cooled:  \r\n   (1) Placing the FOOD in shallow pans; (Pf)\r\n   (2) Separating the FOOD into smaller or thinner portions; (Pf)\r\n   (3) Using rapid cooling EQUIPMENT; (Pf)\r\n   (4) Stirring the FOOD in a container placed in an ice water bath; (Pf)\r\n   (5) Using containers that facilitate heat transfer; (Pf)\r\n   (6) Adding ice as an ingredient; (Pf) or\r\n   (7) Other effective methods. (Pf)  \r\n(B) When placed in cooling or cold holding EQUIPMENT, FOOD containers in which FOOD is being cooled shall be:  \r\n   (1) Arranged in the EQUIPMENT to provide maximum heat transfer through the       container walls; and\r\n   (2) Loosely covered, or uncovered if protected from overhead contamination as          specified under Subparagraph 3-305.11(A)(2), during the cooling period to facilitate    heat transfer from the surface of the FOOD.","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Food item(s) cooled","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Improperly","subProblem":"Covered","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2019-01-25T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Cool items uncovered on the top shelf of cooler."},{"inspectionid":"45010","inspectionDate":"1/25/2019","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"5414","name":"Eatori Market","violationCode":"3-402.12","violationDescription":"If raw, raw-marinated, partially cooked, or marinated-partially cooked FISH are served or sold in READY-TO-EAT form, the PERSON IN CHARGE shall record the freezing temperature and time to which the FISH are subjected and shall retain the records at the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT for 90 calendar days beyond the time of service or sale of the FISH. (Pf)\r\nIf the FISH are frozen by a supplier, a written agreement or statement from the supplier stipulating that the FISH supplied are frozen to a temperature and for a time specified by law. \r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Frozen fish record(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2019-01-30T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide."}]},{"inspectionid":"42705","establishmentid":"5414","name":"Eatori Market","inspectionDate":"2018-06-29T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"124","pcount":"2","pfcount":"2","ccount":"0","criticalcount":"4","noncritical":"0","correctedcritical":"4","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"42705","inspectionDate":"6/29/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"5414","name":"Eatori Market","violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\r\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\r\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \r\n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\r\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"disposable, paper towels","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"RESTROOM (MEN'S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-06-29T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide"},{"inspectionid":"42705","inspectionDate":"6/29/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"5414","name":"Eatori Market","violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-06-29T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store below 41 degrees F."},{"inspectionid":"42705","inspectionDate":"6/29/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"5414","name":"Eatori Market","violationCode":"3-203.12","violationDescription":"SHELLSTOCK tags shall remain attached to the container in which the shellstock are received until the container is empty and tags shall be retained for 90 days after the container is empty.  Retained tags shall be kept in chronological order and correlated to the date when shellstock are harvested. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Shellstock","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Identification","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-06-29T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Retain on file."},{"inspectionid":"42705","inspectionDate":"6/29/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"5414","name":"Eatori Market","violationCode":"3-101.11","violationDescription":"FOOD shall be safe, unADULTERATED and honestly presented. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Food","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Dishonestly presented","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-06-29T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard"}]},{"inspectionid":"40920","establishmentid":"5414","name":"Eatori Market","inspectionDate":"2017-11-27T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"124","pcount":"0","pfcount":"1","ccount":"1","criticalcount":"1","noncritical":"1","correctedcritical":"1","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"40920","inspectionDate":"11/27/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"5414","name":"Eatori Market","violationCode":"3-603.11","violationDescription":"If an animal FOOD such as  beef, EGGS, FISH, lamb, milk, pork, POULTRY, or shellfish is served or sold raw, undercooked, or without otherwise being processed to eliminate pathogens, either in a READY-TO-EAT form or as an ingredient in another READY-TO-EAT FOOD, the PERMIT HOLDER shall inform CONSUMERS of the significantly increased RISK of consuming such FOODS, by using menu advisories, brochures, lable statements, table tents, placards, or other effective written means. (Pf)\r\nFOOD LAW SEC 6149\r\n...The food establishment may provide the following statement on selection information so that it is made pulblicly available: \"Ask your server about menu items that are cooked to order or served raw.  Consuming raw or undercooked, meats, poultry, shellfish, or eggs may increase your risk of foodborne illness.\"\r\nThe statements must be in a minimum of 11 point font and in a color that provides a clear contrast to background.\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Menu advisories","subItem":"for raw or undercooked food(s)/ingredient(s) meat","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-12-20T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"inspectionid":"40920","inspectionDate":"11/27/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"5414","name":"Eatori Market","violationCode":"5-501.17","violationDescription":"A toilet room used by females shall be provided with a covered receptacle for sanitary napkins.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Covered waste receptacle(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."}]},{"inspectionid":"40205","establishmentid":"5414","name":"Eatori Market","inspectionDate":"2017-09-27T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Plan Review/Pre-Open","inspectorid":"122","pcount":"3","pfcount":"1","ccount":"13","criticalcount":"4","noncritical":"13","correctedcritical":"4","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"40205","inspectionDate":"9/27/2017","inspectionType":"Plan Review/Pre-Open","establishmentid":"5414","name":"Eatori Market","violationCode":"5-202.12","violationDescription":"(A) A handwashing sink shall be equipped to provide water at a temperature of at least 38°C (100°F) through a mixing valve or combination faucet. (Pf)  \r\n(B) A steam mixing valve may not be used at a handwashing sink.  \r\n(C) A self-closing, slow-closing, or metering faucet shall provide a flow of water for at least 15 seconds without the need to reactivate the faucet.   \r\n(D) An automatic handwashing facility shall be installed in accordance with manufacturer's instructions.\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Handwashing facility","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Lack of hot water","subProblem":"","location":"BASEMENT","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-12T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide hot water."},{"inspectionid":"40205","inspectionDate":"9/27/2017","inspectionType":"Plan Review/Pre-Open","establishmentid":"5414","name":"Eatori Market","violationCode":"6-101.11","violationDescription":"Materials for indoor floor, wall, and ceiling surfaces under conditions of normal use shall be:\r\n(1) SMOOTH, durable, and EASILY CLEANABLE for areas where FOOD ESTABLISHMENT operations are conducted;\r\n(2) Closely woven and EASILY CLEANABLE carpet for carpeted areas; and\r\n(3) Nonabsorbent for areas subject to moisture such as FOOD preparation areas, walk-in refrigerators, WAREWASHING areas, toilet rooms, mobile FOOD ESTABLISHMENT SERVICING AREAS, and areas subject to flushing or spray cleaning methods.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Floor material(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not easily cleanable","subProblem":"Floor is rough with peeling paint","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-12T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to be easily cleanable."},{"inspectionid":"40205","inspectionDate":"9/27/2017","inspectionType":"Plan Review/Pre-Open","establishmentid":"5414","name":"Eatori Market","violationCode":"5-402.11","violationDescription":"Except as otherwise allowed, a direct connection may not exist between the SEWAGE system and a drain originating from EQUIPMENT in which FOOD, portable EQUIPMENT, or UTENSILS are placed. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Backflow/backsiphonage prevention device(s)","subItem":"Air gap","problemDescription":"Not provided on","subProblem":"Ice holding bin","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-12T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide adequate air gap."},{"inspectionid":"40205","inspectionDate":"9/27/2017","inspectionType":"Plan Review/Pre-Open","establishmentid":"5414","name":"Eatori Market","violationCode":"4-903.11","violationDescription":"Cleaned EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS, laundered LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES shall be stored in an approved manner and location.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Clean equipment/utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Exposed to dust, splash, or other contaminates","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-12T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store in manner that does not contaminate items"},{"inspectionid":"40205","inspectionDate":"9/27/2017","inspectionType":"Plan Review/Pre-Open","establishmentid":"5414","name":"Eatori Market","violationCode":"6-501.11","violationDescription":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Physical facilities","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"BAR","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-12T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair"},{"inspectionid":"40205","inspectionDate":"9/27/2017","inspectionType":"Plan Review/Pre-Open","establishmentid":"5414","name":"Eatori Market","violationCode":"4-402.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT that is fixed because it is not EASILY MOVABLE shall be installed so that it is spaced to allow access for cleaning along the sides, behind, and above the EQUIPMENT or sealed as required,  COUNTER-MOUNTED EQUIPMENT that is not EASILY MOVABLE shall be installed to allow cleaning of the EQUIPMENT and areas underneath and around the EQUIPMENT .\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Fixed equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not sealed to adjoining","subProblem":"Wall(s)","location":"COFFEE AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-12T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Seal to wall/equipment to facilitate cleaning."},{"inspectionid":"40205","inspectionDate":"9/27/2017","inspectionType":"Plan Review/Pre-Open","establishmentid":"5414","name":"Eatori Market","violationCode":"5-204.11","violationDescription":"A HANDWASHING SINK shall be located: \r\n(A) To allow convenient use by EMPLOYEES in FOOD preparation, FOOD dispensing, and WAREWASHING areas;  (Pf)and\r\n(B) In, or immediately adjacent to, toilet rooms. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Handwashing sink(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"COFFEE AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-12T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide hand sink in same room as food handling."},{"inspectionid":"40205","inspectionDate":"9/27/2017","inspectionType":"Plan Review/Pre-Open","establishmentid":"5414","name":"Eatori Market","violationCode":"4-402.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT that is fixed because it is not EASILY MOVABLE shall be installed so that it is spaced to allow access for cleaning along the sides, behind, and above the EQUIPMENT or sealed as required,  COUNTER-MOUNTED EQUIPMENT that is not EASILY MOVABLE shall be installed to allow cleaning of the EQUIPMENT and areas underneath and around the EQUIPMENT .\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Fixed equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not spaced to allow access for cleaning","subProblem":"Wall(s)","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-12T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide adequate space for cleaning."},{"inspectionid":"40205","inspectionDate":"9/27/2017","inspectionType":"Plan Review/Pre-Open","establishmentid":"5414","name":"Eatori Market","violationCode":"4-402.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT that is fixed because it is not EASILY MOVABLE shall be installed so that it is spaced to allow access for cleaning along the sides, behind, and above the EQUIPMENT or sealed as required,  COUNTER-MOUNTED EQUIPMENT that is not EASILY MOVABLE shall be installed to allow cleaning of the EQUIPMENT and areas underneath and around the EQUIPMENT .\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Fixed equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not spaced to allow access for cleaning","subProblem":"Wall(s)","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-12T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide adequate space for cleaning."},{"inspectionid":"40205","inspectionDate":"9/27/2017","inspectionType":"Plan Review/Pre-Open","establishmentid":"5414","name":"Eatori Market","violationCode":"6-303.11","violationDescription":"Light of the proper intensity shall be provided as specified.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Lighting intensity","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Less than","subProblem":"10 foot candles","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-12T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"inspectionid":"40205","inspectionDate":"9/27/2017","inspectionType":"Plan Review/Pre-Open","establishmentid":"5414","name":"Eatori Market","violationCode":"6-501.11","violationDescription":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Physical facilities","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"3 COMPARTMENT SINK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-12T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair"},{"inspectionid":"40205","inspectionDate":"9/27/2017","inspectionType":"Plan Review/Pre-Open","establishmentid":"5414","name":"Eatori Market","violationCode":"4-402.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT that is fixed because it is not EASILY MOVABLE shall be installed so that it is spaced to allow access for cleaning along the sides, behind, and above the EQUIPMENT or sealed as required,  COUNTER-MOUNTED EQUIPMENT that is not EASILY MOVABLE shall be installed to allow cleaning of the EQUIPMENT and areas underneath and around the EQUIPMENT .\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Fixed equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not sealed to adjoining","subProblem":"Wall(s)","location":"3 COMPARTMENT SINK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-12T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Seal to wall/equipment to facilitate cleaning."},{"inspectionid":"40205","inspectionDate":"9/27/2017","inspectionType":"Plan Review/Pre-Open","establishmentid":"5414","name":"Eatori Market","violationCode":"6-201.13","violationDescription":"(A) In FOOD ESTABLISHMENTS in which cleaning methods other than water flushing are used for cleaning floors, the floor and wall junctures shall be coved and closed to no larger than one thirty-second inch.\r\n(B) The floors in FOOD ESTABLISHMENTS in which water flush cleaning methods are used shall be provided with drains and be graded to drain, and the floor and wall junctures shall be coved and SEALED.","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Floor(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not coved","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-12T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide / install coved molding."},{"inspectionid":"40205","inspectionDate":"9/27/2017","inspectionType":"Plan Review/Pre-Open","establishmentid":"5414","name":"Eatori Market","violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"Broken","location":"3 COMPARTMENT SINK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-12T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."},{"inspectionid":"40205","inspectionDate":"9/27/2017","inspectionType":"Plan Review/Pre-Open","establishmentid":"5414","name":"Eatori Market","violationCode":"5-402.11","violationDescription":"Except as otherwise allowed, a direct connection may not exist between the SEWAGE system and a drain originating from EQUIPMENT in which FOOD, portable EQUIPMENT, or UTENSILS are placed. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Backflow/backsiphonage prevention device(s)","subItem":"Air gap","problemDescription":"Not provided on","subProblem":"Ice machine","location":"BASEMENT","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-12T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide adequate air gap."},{"inspectionid":"40205","inspectionDate":"9/27/2017","inspectionType":"Plan Review/Pre-Open","establishmentid":"5414","name":"Eatori Market","violationCode":"6-201.11","violationDescription":"Except otherwise approved, and except for antislip floor coverings or applications may be used for safety reasons, floors, floor coverings, walls, wall coverings, and ceilings shall be designed, constructed, and installed so they are SMOOTH and EASILY CLEANABLE.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"ceiling(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not constructed, designed, installed to be","subProblem":"Smooth","location":"BASEMENT","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-12T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to be smooth and easily cleanable."},{"inspectionid":"40205","inspectionDate":"9/27/2017","inspectionType":"Plan Review/Pre-Open","establishmentid":"5414","name":"Eatori Market","violationCode":"6-101.11","violationDescription":"Materials for indoor floor, wall, and ceiling surfaces under conditions of normal use shall be:\r\n(1) SMOOTH, durable, and EASILY CLEANABLE for areas where FOOD ESTABLISHMENT operations are conducted;\r\n(2) Closely woven and EASILY CLEANABLE carpet for carpeted areas; and\r\n(3) Nonabsorbent for areas subject to moisture such as FOOD preparation areas, walk-in refrigerators, WAREWASHING areas, toilet rooms, mobile FOOD ESTABLISHMENT SERVICING AREAS, and areas subject to flushing or spray cleaning methods.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Floor material(s)","subItem":"for construction","problemDescription":"Not durable","subProblem":"Floor is rough with peeling paint","location":"BASEMENT","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-12T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to be durable under normal use."}]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"5414"}}